O.k., so the next thing that we're going to do is called an in and out and I'm going to show the ladies their footwork.
Basically this is just a variation of the inside turn footwork that you learned before.
So all we're going to do is change directions.
So instead of going, one, two, three and doing our inside turn this way, now we're going to go, one, two, change directions, and do the inside turn back the way we came, five, six seven, one two, three.
So we do our back, rock on one, two, instead of coming together on three, we're going to step out to the side putting all our weight on the right foot, sticking that hip out a little bit.
Kind of like you're standing at the bus stop.
Alright?
So this is three, now we're going to go back this way, exactly the same inside turn footwork.
So we're going to start with our left foot, turn left, right, left, and basic, back, rock, together, so you end up facing the same way that you started.
One more time all together.
It goes, back, rock, change direction, and turn, six, seven, basic, one, two, three, five, six, seven.